We sell magic mushroom products online.
We did about 650,000 in revenue last year.
What's stopping us is basically marketing.
How much content do you make?
One reel a day, a couple stories.
How many hours per day are you spending on advertising?
Three to four hours a day.
You're making one reel?
Well, okay, maybe.
Yeah, maybe it's not that much.
I don't know.
I'm just thinking, we're figuring out.
It's like I'm only smoking one cigarette a day, doc.
I don't know where this black lung came from.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What are you doing that is more important than that now?
Nothing.
Okay.
Yeah.
Great.
Yeah, yeah.
That's what I figured, yeah.
So number one is you should be cross platforming everything.
So all the reels should be TikTok, YouTube Shorts,
Facebook, LinkedIn, video is blowing up right now.
X actually, video is big there too, so there's six.
Take the transcriptions of those.
Those become posts in of themselves.
Take the transcriptions, make them into infographics.
Those become posts with 21X output.
Second lever is on the production side.
You guys are doing however much per day, one reel per day.
I'm guessing you're like making it and posting it,
making it and posting it.
Yeah.
Does that sound about right?
Okay, so here's this idea.
We're gonna plan the week.
We're gonna spend like two days
just planning what we're gonna make.
And then we're gonna spend one day recording all of it.
And then you can just get into a cadence
that now you can post way more.